I'm trash that doesn't deserve you?
Isn’t that the truth?
The truth?
Livia,
everything you
have, I gave you.
The power I hold
is beyond your comprehension.
You should spend your
whole life on your knees.
Enough!
The engagement's over.
Your delusions change nothing.
You're a joke.
All of Golantis will laugh at you!
A joke?
Not a single person here is worthy of laughing at me.
You’re nothing but a lowly miner.
Any one of us here
could crush you without effort.
Redmond, he’s actually
right about one thing.
Those two miners
he dragged here
are just as low as he is.
Of course they aren’t
qualified to laugh at him.
Oh, I get it now!
You brought your little
dirt-buddies so you wouldn't
feel like the biggest
loser in the room!
Smart!
Hey!
We break our backs
to earn honest money!
We’re not ashamed of it.
No right?
Did this garbage just
talk back to me?
You know I'm right!
Right?
I could kill you right here, and no one would stop me.